The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Thousands of years ago,
the Ancestors of the Burning Fire country
sealed the Fire Spirit Beasts within the volcanoes.
These Fire Spirit Beasts sought vengeance
so they hunted lone cultivators to use as sacrifices
in order to feed a powerful Fire Spirit Beast King.
Once the Fire Spirit Beast King is mature,
they will reduce the Burning Fire country along with its neighbors
to ashes.
Now that the Fire Spirit Beast King has been devoured by the Heaven Defying Bead,
the enraged Fire Spirit Beasts will begin to attack the seals anyways.
I'm glad this seal exists.
Once Lin Tao brings me the map,
I must leave the Burning Fire country.
That spiritual energy fluctuation was very powerful.
What do you think ?
Song Yunzhi\NWar God Shrine Ancestor\NLate stage Nascent Soul
The others might not recognize this
but we all know that
Yang Sen\NWar God Shrine Ancestor\NMiddle stage Nascent Soul
this is the doing of the Fire Spirit Beasts.
It’s far more violent than usual this time.
But if we join forces to subdue these mere beasts,
it won't be a problem.
That's nonsense.
The Fire Spirit Beasts are the fire element
so only water element spells can resist them.
How many water or cold type cultivators do we have ?
How could we...
Zhou Jin\NWar God Shrine Ancestor\NEarly stage Nascent Soul
Since the previous seals were effective,
then this time
we just have to reinforce the seals.
Rather than debating here,
we should act now.
I’ll take my leave first !
Enough,
send the order.
All Ancestors and disciples
are to reinforce the seals on the volcanoes in our territory.
Understood.
I can finally feast to my heart’s content !
Come back here !
I have completed the water and fire elements.
Wood is only halfway done.
With metal and earth, that will be all 5 elements.
I wonder what power this bead will have
when all 5 are complete.
Spare me Master !
Spare me Master ! Please...
If this happens again,
you're dead.
Yes, yes, yes !
How is this guy not dead yet ?
Damn it ! And how did he find me ?
This is weird...
Great Freedom Asura Art
False Earth Escape Technique
The Great Freedom Asura Art has six layers.
Kill people to refine their heart
and use this experience to transform your own heart.
Immerse yourself in the path of ruthlessness to make an Asura Soul.
This soul can replace a Nascent Soul.
Great Freedom Asura Art
False Earth Escape Technique
To cultivate this art,
kill one person per day.
One person per day ?
If he practices this technique,
won’t I have souls to devour every day ?
Congratulations Master,
congratulations.
With such a high-level technique,
your Nascent Soul breakthrough is within reach !
This jade slip came from Sun Youcai’s Senior Brother.
Since you already devoured him,
then this cultivation technique must be mediocre.
Great Freedom Asura Art
False Earth Escape Technique
This jade slip doesn't even contain a voice
and the technique’s name includes the word “false”.
I'm sure it's worthless.
Great Freedom Asura Art
False Earth Escape Technique
Master, the Great Freedom Asura Art is far superior.
Senior Situ told me that the Earth Escape Technique is one of the elemental escapes.
They were famous in the ancient cultivation world.
Even if this one is an imitation,
it shouldn't be underestimated when compared to other spells.
Great Freedom Asura Art
Master,
this technique is just for fleeing.
It’s nowhere near as strong as that killing technique...
Be it his talent or Spirit Root, Ma Liang's body
is far superior to my previous body.
Learning this False Earth Escape Technique felt effortless.
East, west, north, south...
Ice crystals, fall !
Formation, activate !
Senior Brother is amazing !
Indeed !
We couldn't fix the formation after half a month.
But with Senior Brother here,
those fire beasts are no big deal.
We're safe with this formation.
Right !
What’s happening ?!
How did the formation break ?
Senior Brother !
Senior brother has fallen ! Run !
Send a message to the sect !
Big brother,
the volcanoes are erupting one after another.
We cultivators can still evade them
but the mortals have no means to resist.
Wan’er,
now that the Burning Fire country
is filled with this violent fire spiritual energy.
If we cultivators absorb too much of it,
we can lose our minds
and at worst, burn to death.
Do you think we cultivators have anywhere to hide ?
Unless…
All disciples are to return to the sect at once.
I wonder why the Ancestors summoned us.
Lan Ruo\NLuo River Sect Ancestor\NMiddle stage Nascent Soul
You were called here
because of the Fire Spirit Beasts' rampage.
The country is now in chaos.
The Luo River Sect, War God Shrine, Evil Devil Sect and Corpse Sect
have formed the Burning Fire Alliance.
And now,
the Burning Fire Alliance will migrate to the country of Xuanwu.
Burning Fire country
Evil Devil Sect
War God Shrine
Country of Chu
Country of Xuanwu
Cloud Sky Sect
Luo River Sect
Corpse Sect
Xuanwu is crowded with sects.
Will they be willing
to share their resources with us ?
This…
This will likely lead to war.
Indeed.
Ancestor, if all the cultivators migrate
then how will the mortals survive the Fire Spirit Beasts ?
We’ve done our best to evacuate them.
The Dao is merciless
so we must prepare for the worst.
There is no room for debate.
Follow the orders
and prepare to migrate.
This flying sword is quite good.
It's much faster than that iron scrap.
The time has come.
Hide inside.
I can’t wait for Lin Tao anymore,
I need to reach the border.
The Burning Fire country is no longer safe.
Such a powerful Divine Sense !
Damn it, they found me !
These Fire Spirit Beasts resist Divine Sense attacks
and even my flying sword barely hurts them.
All things must have a weakness.
As expected.
I'm going to die !
Master,
this little sword won’t last long.
Calm down.
It seems that I’ll need the power of thousands of cultivators.
Follow me to flank the Fire Spirit Beasts !
Yes !
Who are you ?
State your name !
I am a War God Shrine disciple, Ma Liang.
Qing Xuan, take him to the War God Shrine to confirm.
If he’s not a War God Shrine disciple,
kill him.
Understood.
Qing Xuan of Luo River Sect
escorts Ma Liang of the War God Shrine.
Fellow cultivators, please confirm his identity
so I may report back.
Follow me.
Where did this scoundrel come from ?
How dare you impersonate a War God Shrine disciple !
He destroyed my artifact so easily…
Thank you for your efforts, fellow cultivator Qing Xuan.
Ma Liang is indeed our disciple.
Thank you for escorting him.
Does Master know Ancestor Feng Luan ?
She sent me to bring you to her.
Lead the way.
Lin Tao was caught by Ancestor Feng Luan while copying the map.
The map is in her hands now
and Lin Tao was punished.
Wang Lin pays respects to Senior.
Is Wang Lin your real name ?
Not only did this brat steal a disciple's body
but he also lured the Fire Spirit Beasts here !
Do you know that in this battle,
over a thousand of us died !
I won’t allow you kill him !
I can spare him.
But since he’s not Ma Liang,
he’s no longer our disciple.
He cannot stay here !
Wang Lin, do you want to be my disciple ?
Disciple is willing.
Since Junior Sister Feng Luan is willing to take him as disciple,
I won't pursue this any further.
With the war coming up,
this Foundation Establishment cultivator
likely won't survive long on the battlefield.
Sister Luan, why are you doing this ?
You're the one that sent Hong'er to the Foreign Battlefield
but she encountered many dangers there.
If not for this little friend,
your daughter would have died there !
War God Shrine
This jade is a Nascent Soul-level artifact I crafted years ago.
I've already wiped my Divine Sense from it.
Refine it and use it.
It should protect your life in this war.
Thank you Senior.
After we escape the Burning Fire country
and reach the country of Xuanwu,
the war will be fierce.
We forgive your previous offences.
But I will only help you only once
to repay you for saving Zihong.
Dismissed.
When we reach the country of Xuanwu,
this person will be very useful.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?